talkfusion.com 2019-02-22

# Talk Fusion® PRIVACY POLICY

Talk Fusion® PRIVACY POLICY
Effective January 4, 2019
Talk Fusion, Inc., (“Talk Fusion”, “we”, “us”, and “our”) value your privacy and understand the importance of protecting it.
This “Privacy Policy” applies to Personal Information (as defined below) we collect from you when you visit Talk Fusion’s
corporate website, a “Replicated Website,” of an Independent Associate for Talk Fusion (“Associate”), or the Back-Office
of an Associate, (referred to herein collectively as “Site”). This Site is operated by Talk Fusion, and is hosted on Talk
Fusion’s server as well as on the servers of Talk Fusion’s third-party technology providers. The Personal Information
you submit on this Site is accessed by Talk Fusion and the Associate to whom this Site is assigned (as set forth in this
Privacy Policy). For the purpose of EU data protection laws, Talk Fusion and Associates (depending on your relationship
with Associates) are “data controllers” and are responsible for, and control the processing of, your Personal Information
collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy.
PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION
Through your use of or visits to the Site, we may collect Personal Information you provide to us. “Personal Information”
is any piece of information that can potentially be used to identify, contact, or locate a single person. We may collect the
following Personal Information from you: your name, address, email address, telephone number, social security and
tax identification number, and credit card or banking information, billing address, IP address, images or videos that you
upload to the Site, passport information, date of birth, driver’s license information and purchase history. We may also
collect Personal Information in connection with communications you send us, for example, to report a problem or to
submit questions, concerns, or comments regarding the Site, our products or any related content. Finally, we may collect
Personal Information from surveys, if you choose to respond or participate in such surveys. In addition, Associates may
collect your name, email address and telephone number.
In order to become an Associate or Customer (you can become a “Customer” by purchasing one of Talk Fusion’s product
packages), you must provide biographical and contact information (such as name, mailing address, telephone numbers,
and email address) to us. Associate applicants must also provide Personal Information such as an applicant’s Social
Security Number or Federal Tax ID Number so that we may prepare and file necessary non-employee compensation
forms for the IRS. Associates and Customers are also required to provide payment information (such as credit card or
debit card). We may also collect Associates’ commission and bonus information.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We collect and use your Personal Information to fulfil our legal and contractual obligations with you and to pursue
our legitimate interests, which include: (i) establishing or maintaining our relationship with you; (ii) contacting you and
responding to your requests and inquiries; (iii) providing you with services you have requested; (iv) keeping you informed
of products and services we think may be of interest to you; (v) personalizing your experience with us; (vi) assisting you
while you use the Site; (vii) business administration, including statistical analysis; (viii) improving the Site by helping us
to understand who uses the Site and how they are used; (ix) for fraud prevention and detection; and (x) to comply with
applicable laws, regulations, and codes of practice.
DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Personal Information
We collect and use your Personal Information to fulfil our legal and contractual obligations with you and to pursue
our legitimate interests, which include: (i) establishing or maintaining our relationship with you; (ii) contacting you and
responding to your requests and inquiries; (iii) providing you with services you have requested; (iv) keeping you informed
of products and services we think may be of interest to you; (v) personalizing your experience with us; (vi) assisting you
while you use the Site; (vii) business administration, including statistical analysis; (viii) improving the Site by helping us
to understand who uses the Site and how they are used; (ix) for fraud prevention and detection; and (x) to comply with
applicable laws, regulations, and codes of practice.
1 TALK FUSION® PRIVACY POLICY - Effective January 4, 2019

“Genealogy” Information
As a network marketing company, Talk Fusion provides certain information to Associates regarding the other Associates
and Customers enrolled in an Associate’s downline marketing organization.
•     If you complete a “Contact Me” form, all information provided within that form is sent to the sponsoring Associate.
•     If you join as a Customer, the sponsoring Associate will have access to your name, email address and sales volume
      associated with your purchase.
•     If you join as an Associate, the sponsoring Associate will have access to:
      •    The new Associate’s name
      •    Identification of the product the new Associate purchased
      •    The sales volume associated with the new Associate’s purchase
      •    The downline Associate’s rank
      •    The personal enrollments of the downline Associate made in the past 30 days
      •    The weekly cycles of the personally sponsored Associate
      •    The number of Associates that the downline Associate has personally sponsored
      •    The total active volume of each personally sponsored Associate
Any Associate can see the total leg count of any other Associate in their downline and whether any downline member is
Active and/or qualified.
Personal Information relating to downline Associates is made available to Associates subject to a confidentiality and non-
solicitation covenant in the agreement that each Associate enters into with Talk Fusion. However Talk Fusion does not
warrant that other Associates will adhere to the confidentiality and non-solicitation covenants, and Talk Fusion shall not
be responsible for Associates’ violation of these covenants.
Sales Information
If you make a purchase from an Associate’s Replicated Website, we will provide the Associate to whom Replicated
Website is assigned with your name, contact information, a description of the item(s) purchased, and the sales volume
associated with the purchase.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
Talk Fusion may share aggregated demographic information with our partners, vendors, suppliers, third party providers,
and advertisers. This is not linked to any Personal Information.
Lead Assignment and Associate Locater Features
Talk Fusion occasionally will assign prospective sales and new Associate leads to Associates. In these cases, we will
provide the lead with the appropriate Associate’s name and contact information and/or provide an Associate with the
prospective lead’s name and contact information. If Talk Fusion adds an Associate Locator feature on the Site, in order
to make the Associate Locator feature and the lead assignments effective, the we will provide you with the Associate’s
name and contact information, which may include his/her telephone number, address, and/or email address.
Legally Required Law Enforcement, Judicial and Administrative Agency Disclosures
Talk Fusion will provide Personal Information as necessary to comply with judicial and administrative orders, subpoenas,
civil or criminal investigative demands, administrative and regulatory demands and other legal obligations. In order for
Talk Fusion to conduct business in certain jurisdictions, Talk Fusion may be called upon to disclose certain personally
identifiable and confidential information to regulatory authorities in those jurisdictions. Such information may include,
but is not limited to, income information and personally identifiable information. We will provide such information as we
deem necessary.
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Talk Fusion is located, and this Site is hosted, in the United States. If you are visiting this Site from outside the United
States, please note that any Personal Information you share with us will be stored and processed in the United States.
Unless restricted by law, regulation, contract, or professional standards, we may transfer your Personal Information
outside of the United States to other countries for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
2 TALK FUSION® PRIVACY POLICY - Effective January 4, 2019

If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), we may transfer your Personal Information to countries
outside of the EEA that may not provide a similar or adequate level of protection to that provided by the EEA (including
the United States). To provide adequate protection for Personal Information transferred from the EEA, Talk Fusion relies
on European Commission approved Standard Contractual Clauses.
YOUR RIGHTS
Individuals in the EEA have certain data subject rights which may be subject to limitations and/or restrictions. These rights
include the right to: (i) request access to and rectification or erasure of their Personal Information; (ii) obtain restriction of
processing or to object to processing of their Personal Information; and (iii) ask for a copy of their Personal Information to
be provided to them, or a third party, in a digital format. If you wish to exercise one of the above-mentioned rights, please
send us your request to the contact details set out below. Individuals also have the right to lodge a complaint about the
processing of their Personal Information with their local data protection authority.
COMMUNICATIONS
Communication from Talk Fusion and from Upline Associates
Talk Fusion sends all new Associates and Customers a welcoming email to verify identification numbers. All Associates
and Customers will occasionally receive information on the Talk Fusion business, products, services, special deals, and
a newsletter. An Associate in another Associate’s upline may contact a downline Associate via the downline message
feature from within the upline Associate’s account, they can choose to send a video email message to their downline,
including but not limited to inactive Associates. This message is delivered by Talk Fusion to the email address on file
within the person’s account. The sending Associate is NOT provided with the personal email of all the Associates in their
downline.
Customers may receive communication via any form of media from their Associate.
Contact by Other Associates
Associates may be contacted by their sponsor or other upline Associate.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is
temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send Associates and/or Customers an email.
Customer Service
Talk Fusion communicates with Associates and Customers via email, regular mail, text, social media and telephone
on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their Talk Fusion business. Talk
Fusion communicates with Customers with respect to products or services purchased by such Customers from Talk
Fusion. Such communications may be by email, regular mail, text message, social media or telephone. Talk Fusion also
communicates with Associates through leaving messages in Associates’ Back-Offices.
MISCELLANEOUS
Information Collection and Use
I understand that Talk Fusion is the sole owner of the information collected on this site and that they will not sell, share,
or rent this information to others. By purchasing or using any Talk Fusion Product or Service, I authorize Talk Fusion
to use my brand, name, video, photograph, personal story and/or likeness in advertising or promotional materials and
waive all claims for remuneration for such use.
Retention of Personal Information
We retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless
a longer retention period is required or allowed by law, including to fulfil a legal obligation.
3 TALK FUSION® PRIVACY POLICY - Effective January 4, 2019

Google Information
Talk Fusion may access users’ Google account information to import Google contacts into our Talk Fusion Suite Contact
Manager.
Security
Talk Fusion implements and maintains reasonable physical, administrative and technical security measures to protect
your Personal Information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also seek to protect your information off-line.
All Personal Information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the Personal Information to perform
a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a Customer service representative) are granted access to Personal
Information. Furthermore, our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices and trained
accordingly.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Talk Fusion reserves the right to amend or change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole discretion. When material
changes or amendments are made to the Privacy Policy, we will announce the same under the Privacy Policy tab for a
period of at least 30 days prior to implementation of the amended Privacy Policy.
Third Party Links
This Site may contain links to or from other sites. Please be aware that Talk Fusion is not responsible for the privacy
practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy
statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies
solely to information collected by Talk Fusion websites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain
information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To
make such a request, you may contact us as described below.
Cookies
Our Site uses “cookies” to enhance your experience while using the Site. Your web browser places cookies on your
hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you. You may choose to set your
web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that certain Site
features may not function properly.
“Do Not Track” disclosure
Certain web browsers may allow you to enable a “do not track” option that sends signals to the websites you visit
indicating that you do not want your online activities tracked. This is different than blocking cookies as browsers with the
“do not track” option selected may still accept cookies. We currently do not honor “do not track” signals. If we do so in
the future, we will update this Privacy Policy accordingly.
Children’s Privacy
This Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, do not use this Site. We do not
knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected or received
Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that
information.
Dispute Resolution
This privacy policy is governed by the law of the State of Florida. Exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any dispute arising
from or relating to this Agreement shall be in the courts of the State of Florida residing in Hillsborough County, or the
United States District Court for the Middle District of Florida, Tampa Division.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, if you have a claim arising from or relating to this Agreement that is within the
jurisdictional amount of your local U.S. Small Claims Court, You may bring such action before the small claims court in
the U.S. jurisdiction in which you reside.
4 TALK FUSION® PRIVACY POLICY - Effective January 4, 2019

Class Waiver
The parties to this privacy policy waive the right to seek relief under a class or consolidated action. All
claims shall be brought and prosecuted on an individual, rather than a consolidated, or class basis. You may
opt out of this class waiver by sending written notice to Talk Fusion of your desire to opt out within 30 days
from the date on which you subscribe to the Products and Services. Opt out notices should be sent to Talk
Fusion at 1319 Kingsway Road, Brandon, FL 33510.
Contact Us
If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@talkfusion.com or by mail at:
Talk Fusion
1319 Kingsway Road
Brandon, FL 33510
5 TALK FUSION® PRIVACY POLICY - Effective January 4, 2019
